backpack.tf 2017-09-23

# Privacy Policy - backpack.tf

Your privacy is important to us. We've developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose and store your information. 

## Collection of Personal Data

First and foremost, you will never be asked to provide any of your personal information to access our services. 

The majority of our data comes from the official Steam APIs. This information is considered to be made publicly available by you. 

## Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information

We also collect non-personal information - data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The following are some examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it: 

  * We may collect information about your inventory like the number of slots in a Team Fortress 2 backpack or a Dota 2 armory, which helps us determine if you are a free player or have upgraded your account. 
  * We may also collect information regarding the content of your inventory. We use this information to create the complex statistics that show up on various statistical pages throughout the website. 

This data is provided on an opt-in basis, as our ability to gather this data depends on your inventory privacy setting via the Steam Community website. 

## Cookies and Other Technologies

Our website and advertisers may use "cookies" and other technologies such as pixel tag and web beacons. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which part of our website people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

Our website also uses "cookies" and other technologies to remember personal information when you use our website. Our goal in these cases is to make your experience with our website more convenient and personal. For example, knowing your favorite "currency" can help us make this the default option when you view someone's inventory.

As is true of most websites, we gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

## Analytics

We’ve implemented Google Analytics based on Display Advertising (e.g. Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting). 

We and third-party vendors, including Google, will use this remarketing information and data based on previous visits to our site to serve relevant messages across the web. 

You can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's Ads Settings. Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page. 

## 3rd party cookies

We uses cookies on our websites in order to provide enhanced functionality to users, such as user accounts and saved preferences. We also use cookies to ensure that you see the most relevant ads and limit the number of times we show you the same advertisements. 

If you continue to use this site, we'll assume you are happy to accept these cookies. Some of the adverts carried on our websites are delivered by third party servers and in doing so they may leave cookies on your machine. 

You may opt-out of these cookies by following these links: 

MediaMind opt-out: <http://ds.serving-sys.com/OBA/Europe/Opt-out.aspx>

FlashTalking opt-out: <http://www.flashtalking.com/cookieOptOut.html>

MindShare opt-out: <http://www.mindshareworld.com/privacy>

## Requesting Removal of a Specific Inventory

While we could offer a way to make an inventory private from others to see from our services, you would not be blocking every other backpack explorers that currently exist. If you would like your inventory to be private, we strongly suggest that you specify this option from your steam profile directly. Please [follow this link](https://support.steampowered.com/kb_article.php?ref=4113-YUDH-6401) to the steam support knowledgebase for exact instructions. This is the only safe way to have your inventory private. We do not recommend this, as it will limit your ability to use certain 3rd party sites, but if you feel your privacy is at risk then we strongly recommend you follow these steps. It is a personal choice, after all. 

## Service Guarantees

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice.
